sakshieducation.com 2017-12-02

# Sakshieducation: Disclaimer

The following are the terms and conditions for accessing and using [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) and all its related pages/products such as apps.The website [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) developed and operated by Jagati Publications Ltd, at Sakshi School of Journalism, #8-2-696, 697/75/1, Road No. 12, Banjara Hills, Hyderabad-500034, is offered to the user/s (hereinafter ‘visitor/s’) upon the terms and conditions that follow.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) is an online education portal that allows visitors to read and otherwise use the content for personal knowledge and not for any commercial purposes. Wherever necessary, we may ask the visitors to provide their personal information to identify. This is only for our own records purpose and we won't share any visitor's details with any third party for any commercial purposes.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [education@sakshi.com](mailto:education@sakshi.com).

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) updates from time to time. [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in connecting with other users of similar interests.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

We may also use a user’s email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their “notification” setting to “Do not send me notification emails” in the user “Account Settings”.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set — each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences — however, you must enable cookies from [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) in order to use most functions on the site.

Please note that [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertiser’s use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) Privacy Policy.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) contains links to sites and is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/).

Members who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may choose not to by selecting the appropriate options in the user profile ‘Account Settings’. All notification emails and [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

Ads appearing on [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) may be delivered to our users of our partner websites. Our web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) does not rent, sell, or share personal information about its visitors with other people (save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) communicate with you about offers from [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) and our publication partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/)‘s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A visitor is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use a visitor’s personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our website for 30 days.

The content, material, suggestions, advice, links and any other information provided by [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) is collected from various sources such as websites, newspapers, employment notifications, authors, subject experts and others. While all care and caution have been taken to ensure accuracy of information, [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) does not warrant that the content contained in the material available on or comprised in the website will be uninterrupted or error-free. The website shall not be liable for loss or damage or other inconvenience suffered by anyone as a result of using any information provided in this site. This site should be viewed purely as a source of information and should not be taken to guarantee or warranty for performance of any activity. Users must get it clarified from the official sources before coming to a conclusion on the information provided on the website.

The visitor understands that except for the information, products and services clearly identified as being provided by [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/), and [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) does not endorse any information and will not be responsible for errors in the information provided. The content may be changed at any time without notice.

Material on this site is protected by copyright. You must not make any alterations or additions to the material on this site, or sell it or misappropriate it. Information can be downloaded or copied for personal or educational use. You should properly acknowledge [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) if you re-publish material from this website.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) and Jagati Publications Ltd. do not store or keep credit card data in a location that is accessible via the Internet. Once a credit card transaction has been completed, all credit card data is moved off-line only to ensure that the data/credit card information received is not accessible to anyone after completion of the on-line transaction and to ensure the maximum security. [sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) and Jagati Publications Ltd. take maximum care as is possible to ensure that all or any data / information in respect of electronic transfer of money does not fall in the wrong hands.

[sakshieducation.com](http://sakshieducation.com/) and Jagati Publications Ltd. shall not be liable for any loss or damage sustained by reason of any disclosure (inadvertent or otherwise) of any information concerning the user’s account and/or information relating to or regarding online transactions using credit cards/debit cards and/or their verification process and particulars nor for any error, omission or inaccuracy with respect to any information so disclosed and used whether or not in pursuance of a legal process or otherwise.

**By accessing and browsing the site, you accept these Terms and Conditions.**
